enkord.com 2011-05-30

# Privacy Policy for Enkord

Any personal information that you provide to our Web site will stay safe, private, and secure. We will not resell your information to outside sources.

We will not share your information with any third parties with the exception of verified secure ecommerce transaction providers.

**Information that we may collect from our users**

We may collect the following information when you sign up for a service:

* First name, last name, e-mail, address, phone number

**IP Address:**

When a user visits our website, we may collect the IP address that requested the display of our site. This address is collected for two purposes. The first purpose is to exercise our ability to restrict access to the site by users who have violated our [Terms of Use](http://www.enkord.com/help/terms/). The second purpose is to support our advertising partners, so that the partners will be able to accurately count the number of unique visitors to our sites who may have viewed a given advertisement.

**Sign Up and Survey information:**

Any information you provide to us as part of your use of our website will be stored as entered.

**Cookies:**

The sole purpose of cookies is to enhance your online experience. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer by websites. Through your web browser, cookies are only used by the website that wrote the cookie. Data stored in a cookie from Enkord is only accessible by the Enkord site. The information in our cookies is kept private and secure.

**Use of collected information**

Your username, e-mail address, and password will be used to uniquely identify you as a user on Enkord site. We may use or display your username for the purposes of rankings, competitions, lottery winnings, chat identification, or game high scores.

Other identifying information collected during the sign up process or through other voluntary means (e.g., via Surveys) may be used to calculate aggregate demographics figures and/or facilitate our ability to direct advertisements to your web browser.

**Other information collected**

Your Web browser or client software that you use to access Enkord may transmit certain geographic information and information regarding the capabilities or features of your computer and/or software to us. We may also track other types of information, such as what games users play, how long our users have been members of any Enkord businesses or programs, the last time a user visited Enkord. We may use this information to calculate aggregate statistics about our user community or for security purposes, and may provide information such information to advertisers and/or partners in aggregate form only. 

**How information is used**

The information you provide to Enkord will allow us to notify you about new features, enhancements, resolution of site problems, handle and/or route your customer support questions and issues, and inform you of upgrade opportunities, contests, prizes, or special events. Enkord may use personal information in combination with data from third parties for similar purposes as well.

**Third-party advertising**

It is important that you understand that advertisers or websites that link to an Enkord site may collect personal information about you. The Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of other advertisers or websites. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our site. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other sites in order to help them provide relevant ads to users (this information does not include name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number).

**Chat & Messaging**

Enkord site may choose to operate message boards and/or chat areas where users can exchange ideas and communicate with one another. When posting to a message board or chat area, it is important for you to understand that the information is being made publicly available in an online environment. Any information posted is the sole responsibility of the individual user.

**Agreement with Enkord policies**

By using any of the Enkord websites, products, or services, you signify your understanding and agreement to the Privacy Policy stated here, and to the [Terms of Use](http://www.enkord.com/help/terms/). If you do not agree with our policies, please do not use any of the Enkord websites, products, or services.
